她是女主角
She is the star of the play,
又是我的女朋友
and she is my girlfriend.
我竟能跟女主角滚床单
I get to have sex with the star of the play!
-别人都能听见  -我故意的
- People can hear you. - I know!
她很漂亮吧
She looks great, doesn't she?
那个男的可真帅
That is one good-looking man.
是我眼花  还是他的腹肌发达得
Is it just me, or can you actually
穿着外套都看得出来
see his abs through his overcoat?
你干这行很久了吗
So you been doing this long?
不  你是第一个  把钱放在桌上
No. You're my first. Put the money on the table.
真不赖
That's nice.
不是吧
Dude!
这件上衣很贵吗
Is that an expensive blouse?
你说贵就贵
If you want it to be.
你女朋友的钮扣
Here's your girlfriend's button.
莫妮卡  你上高中时穿的
Mon, do you still have like your
旧衣服和旧裙子还留着呢吗
old blouses and dresses from high school?
应该还有几件吧  怎么了
Yeah, I think I have some around here somewhere. Why?
我就是觉得吧  孕妇装都好贵啊
Well, it's just maternity clothes are so expensive.
瑞秋  那一堆是你的东西
Rach, I made a pile of your stuff on this side of the room.
看你要不要...
If you could just...
把皮包砸在上面
throw your purses at it.
布明岱尔百货裁减了我的部门
Bloomingdale's eliminated my department.
天哪  你失业了吗
Oh, my God. Are you out of a job?
没有  但我被塞到专人采购部
No, but they stuck me in Personal Shopping,
一下子降了好几级
which is a huge step down.
专人采购部是干什么的
Personal Shopping, what is that?
是不是陪那些盛气凌人的富翁逛商场
Where you walk around with snouty rich people
向他们推销产品
and tell them what to buy?
是啊
Yeah.
这活儿真不错
That sounds great!
拜托  我们交换了公寓
Excuse me. We switched apartments.
不许再来蹭吃蹭喝  没有免费的午餐
You can't eat our food anymore. That gravy train has ended.
还有午餐呢
There's gravy?
住的房子大
If you have the big apartment,
就得应付人来人往
you have to deal with people coming over all the time.
冰箱里必须常备着食品和饮料
That fridge has to be stocked.
对面现在是你们住了
That's your apartment now.
你干什么?
What are you doing?
我好像在这里藏过一只甜甜圈
I think I left a doughnut up here.
凯西的戏怎样
How was Kathy's play?
凯西在台上半裸着
Kathy gets half-naked and simulates sex
跟一个大帅哥演床戏
with a real good-looking guy.
这就好比有人把我的恶梦写成戏
It's like somebody literally wrote down my worst nightmare...
还要我花32块去看
and then charged me $32 to see it.
这个点子有赚头
That's a good idea for a business.
我完蛋了
I'm totally screwed, okay?
他们会夜夜在台上打得火热
They're gonna be hot and heavy on stage every night...
然后去参加剧组派对的时候
then they'll go to their little cast parties,
他一定会设法中伤我
and he's gonna try to undermine me.
也许他会问  "你男朋友呢
You know, he'll be like, "So, where's your boyfriend?
他叫什么  钱斯特吗"
What's his name? Chester?"
她会说  "不  是钱德勒"
And she'll go, "No, no, no. It's Chandler."
然后他便说  "反正都差不多"
And he'll go, "Whatever!"
这招的确不错
That is a good trick.
帮我想想  我该怎么办
All right, look. What am I going to do?
钱德勒  想开点  他们是演员
Chandler. Look, they're actors.
演戏是本职工作
They're there to do a job.
假戏不一定
Just because they work together
就会真做
doesn't mean they're gonna get together.
发生在苏珊·莎兰登
I mean, just because it happened with like
和提姆·罗宾斯身上的事情
Susan Sarandon and Tim Robbins...
不一定会发生在他们身上
doesn't mean it's gonna happen with them.
还有亚历克·鲍德温和金·贝辛格
Alec Baldwin and Kim Basinger.
汤姆·克鲁斯和妮可·基德曼
Tom Cruise and Nicole Kidman.
梅尔·吉布森和克林特·伊斯特伍德
Mel Gibson and Clint Eastwood.
他们又不是一对
They're not a couple.
我终于明白你们在玩什么了
Okay, I get the game now.
我来问你个问题
Look, let me ask you a question.
他们演床戏时很有激情吗
When they were doing it on stage, was it like really hot?
既然是这样  你就放心吧
Well, okay, so you're fine.
表演界金科玉律  若演员私底下是一对
The rule is when two actors are actually doing it off-stage...
到了舞台上  他们之间的火花就会消失
then all the sexual tension between them is gone.
所以只要台上很火热
As long as it's hot on stage,
你就完全不必担心
you got nothing to worry about.
而如果哪一天热度不见了  你就真完蛋了
It's when the heat goes away, that's when you're in trouble.
真的
Really?
你们看过我演的每出戏
You guys have been to every play I've been in.
我在台上跟别人擦出过火花吗
Have I ever had chemistry on stage?
-没有  -对吧
- No. - No!
你晚上陪我去看戏吗
So, man, are you gonna go see the play with me tonight?
我觉得让我去评断你女朋友跟其他男人
I don't know how comfortable I am going to see
滚床单滚得有多激情  会很尴尬的
how hot the sex is between some guy and your girlfriend.
-我知道  但是  -不用说了  我也听见了
- I know, but... - No, I'm there.
莫妮卡  吃煎饼吗
Mon, want some pancakes?
你竟然会做煎饼
You made pancakes?
当然  拿个盘子
Yep. Grab a plate.
别过来  待在那儿
No, no. Stay right there.
越来越近了
Getting closer.
没关系  大家别担心...
Okay, okay. But don't worry...
因为我们还有麦片  松糕  华夫饼
because we also have cereals, muffins, waffles
以及果酱  果肉酱和果皮酱
and jams, jellies and marmalades,
我觉得其实是同一种东西
which I'm fairly certain the same thing.
还有  我们每周六晚看球赛
Listen, also, we're watching the game here Saturday night,
欢迎大家加入
if people wanna come over.
我也正想邀请你们到对面看球呢
I was thinking about having people over for the game.
是吗  谁跟谁比
Yeah? Who's playing?
球员跟球员
The players.
某些人好像很怀念当女主人的感觉
Somebody seems to be missing being the hostess.
拜托  我不知道有多轻松
Please. It's a relief, is what it is, is what it is.
菲比  盘子准备
Pheebs, stick out your plate.
莫妮卡  我要辞职
Monica, I'm quitting.
我刚才帮一个81岁的老女人穿上丁字裤
I just helped an 81-year-old woman put on a thong,
结果她也没买
and she didn't even buy it.
我心意已决  我要辞职  就这样吧
I'm telling you. I'm quitting. That's it.
我现在就去跟老板说
I'm talking to my boss right now.
我去了  我去了  我去了...
Yes, I am. Yes, I am....
好了  听到留言请回电
Okay, bye. Call me when you get this message.
沃森先生  我有事找你
Mr. Waltham? I really need to talk to you.
请一会儿再说  我忙得不可开交
In a moment, please. I'm in the middle of a task.
有顾客上门找你
And you have a customer.
你好  我是约书亚
Hi, I'm Joshua.
你好  我是瑞秋·格林
Hi, I'm Rachel Greene.
您有什么需要  约书亚
What could I do for you, Joshua?
我的衣服都要重买
I need a whole new wardrobe.
我老婆  不对  是我的前妻...
My wife...ell, my ex-wife...
真为你遗撼
I'm so sorry.
她把我的衣服都烧了
Anyway, she burned all of my clothes.
我只救回两件
I got away with two things,
这件西服外套和一条裙子
this suit and what turned out to be a skirt.
至少这件外套很好看
Well, at least that's a great suit.
穿裙子去干洗店
It wasn't much fun dropping it off
洗西装可不是什么好玩的事
at the dry cleaners in the skirt.
我全身上下的衣服都需要  连内衣裤都要
I need everything down to underwear.
如果你愿意  我的一切都交给你打理了
If you're willing, I'm all yours.
好
Okay.
瑞秋  你有事找我
You needed to speak to me?
没有  不是我
No, no, that wasn't me.
我们开始购物吧
We should get started.
我先带你看看我的内衣...
Let me show you my underwear.
我的意思是我们的内衣专柜
The selection of underwear that we carry.
对不起  是这边
I'm sorry. It's this way.
这边吗  抱歉
This way? Sorry.
我猜得没错  对吧
I'm right. Right?
他们在台上一点火花也撞不出来了
There was like no chemistry between them.
之前的热度不见了
Before, they had heat. Now, there's no heat.
你知道个中含意
You know what this means.
乔伊说过
Joey told us what this means.
先别急着下定论  好不好
Let's not jump to any conclusions, all right?
他们之间还是有零星的火花的
There was some sexual chemistry between them.
拜托  简直像是表兄妹在滚床单
Come on. It was like cousins having sex out there.
她来了  什么都别说  冷静
Here she comes. Don't say a word. Okay, just be cool.
别像以前那么毛躁
Don't be, you know, you.
你们好
Hey, you guys!
谢谢你们  又来看我的戏
Thank you so much for coming again.
-你喜欢吗  -那当然
- Did you like it tonight? - Absolutely.
尼克划不着火柴的时候  好不好笑
Wasn't Nick funny when he couldn't get his match lit?
这是一出好戏吧
It's a good play, isn't it?
我很喜欢  你演得很棒
I loved the play. You were great.
尼克也是
And Nick, ditto.
很显然  你跟他有一腿
Clearly, you're having sex with him.
你们慢聊...
Okay...
你说我显然跟他有一腿
Clearly, I'm having sex with him?
拜托  这也太明显了
Oh, come on. It was so obvious.
你们俩在台上毫无激情可言
There was no chemistry between you two.
好  让我理理清楚
Okay, let me just get this straight.
你既指责我不忠
You're accusing me of cheating on you,
同时又侮辱我的演技
and you're insulting my performance?
不过这也难怪
You know, I can see how this could happen.
你们每晚都光着身体  爱抚  热吻
You're up there every night naked, touching, kissing.
钱德  那是在演戏  我是名演员啊
Acting. Chandler, this is my job.
我在台上饰演戏剧中的一个角色
I'm playing a part in a play.
你怎么可以不信任我
How can you not trust me?
你应该能理解吧  我们就是这样开始的
You can understand, given how we started.
你居然用这件事来指责我
I can't believe you're throwing that in my face.
可事实就是如此
Well, that is what happened.
何况你竟然也没否认
And I don't even see you denying this.
够了  钱德  送你一句话
I'll tell you what, Chandler.
等你成熟了  再跟我联络
Why don't you call me when you grow up.
那你可有得等了
Yeah, well, don't expect that to happen any time soon!
世界上没有人比我的工作更好了
I have the best job in the entire world!
今天店里来了个最帅的帅哥
The most adorable guy came over today,
我一整天都在为他打扮
and I got to dress him up all day!
瑞秋有个新洋娃娃了
Rachel has a new doll!
真希望他是个娃娃
I wish he was a doll.
那样我就可以再买一个瑞秋娃娃
Then I could get a Rachel doll
把他跟瑞秋娃娃凑在一起
and then bump them together...
让它们玩亲亲
and make kissing noises.
而且他的名字也是世上最美的
And he's got the most beautiful name.
我以前都不觉得  约书亚
I never realized. Joshua.
约书...亚
Joshua.
约书亚  约书...
Joshua. Josh.
你好啊
Hello?
什么味道?
What do I smell?
不晓得  好香啊
I don't know. It smells good.
热腾腾的饼干  刚出炉的
Fresh cookies! Hot from the oven.
都来尝尝吧
Please, have some.
我闲得无聊
I've been fiddling around here,
就做了点好吃的  让各位饱饱口福
making delicious treats for everyone.
新一期的《花花公子》
The new Playboy.
我随手买的
Just something I picked up.
饼干和黄色书刊  你是史上最酷的妈妈
Cookies and porn? You're the best mom ever!
怎么了
What?
就是突然想起约书亚对V字领的几句评价
It's just something Joshua said about V-necks,
不过现场听他讲  才好玩
but you had to be there.
杰森穿V字领好看吗
How does Jason look in a V-neck?
-是约书亚  -反正都差不多
- It's Joshua. - Oh. Whatever.
等等  饼干不许外带的
Wait. Wait. This isn't takeout!
我必须得走了
Hate to eat and run.
别  求你们了  别走
No, wait. Please, don't go!
也有女生看的黄色杂志
I've got porn for you too.
我不需要
I don't need it.
大家都应该喜欢赖在这里的
People are supposed to want to hang out here.
亲爱的  你怎么了  有什么大不了的
Why? Honey, what is the big deal?
我才是女主人
I'm the hostess.
当主人的一直是我  而不是那几个男的
Not those guys. I'm always the hostess.
就连小的时候
Even when I was little, I mean,
也都是别人抱着洋娃娃来参加我办的茶会
the girls brought their dollies to my tea party.
我这儿的气氛最好
I served the best air.
那你干嘛还大张旗鼓地叫大家
Why'd you make a whole big thing out of
去那边较大的公寓做客呢
you know, everyone has to hanging out in the big apartment?
因为他们抢走了我们的公寓
'Cause they took our apartment.
我想给他们找点不自在
I wanted to punish them.
我的目的达到了  他们吃到苦头了
I'm done now. They've suffered enough.
你要真想惩罚他们
If you wanted to punish them,
应该逼他们来这里待着
you should have just made them hang out here.
那倒是
That is true.
好吧  等我离开这个地方的时候
All right then, when I'm finish with this place,
这里绝对要比对面好十倍
it's gonna be 10 times better than that place.
我们要捣毁对面吗
Are we gonna trash their place?
该死的台阶
There's steps!
臭婆娘
Slut!
凯西真的跟那个人上床了
You'll all be very happy to hear
你们听到一定欢欣鼓舞吧
that Kathy is sleeping with that guy!
-什么  -你猜对了
- What? - You were right?
我当面质问她  她没有否认
I confronted her, and she didn't deny it.
我不住这里
I don't live here!
-钱德  -等等  你确定吗
- Chandler. - Wait, are you sure?
我是醉了  但我听得懂她的话
I may be drunk, but I know what she said.
所以我跑去朱理牛排...
So then I went over to Beefsteak Chewley's...
-是查理牛排吗  -对
- Beefsteak Charlie's? - Yes!
瞧  咱俩一向都很...
See, you and I have always been like:
-需要帮忙吗  -不用  我来就行了
- Do you need help with that? - Nah, I got it.
真惭愧  我从来没吸过地板
I just feel bad. I never vacuum.
今天我跟约书亚相处了一个小时
So, I was with Joshua for an hour today,
他却没有向我提出要约会
and he has not asked me out.
-真泄气  -那就你约他嘛
- Just so frustrating. - Why don't you ask him out?
没错  这绝对会勾起男人的欲望
Oh, yeah. Totally. That's such a turn-on.
是吗  不会显得很饥渴吗
Really? It doesn't seem desperate?
所以才能吊起男人的胃口啊
That's the turn-on.
他刚离婚  对吧
He just got a divorce. Right?
所以他跟女人相处可能会紧张
So he's probably really nervous around women.
也许你需要先主动出击一回嘛
You know, maybe you just need to make the first move.
可是我没约过男生
I've never asked a guy out before.
你没约过男生
You've never asked a guy out?
没有  你有吗
No. Have you?
数都数不清了
Thousands of times!
这也不是什么光荣的事  是吧
That doesn't make me sound too good, does it?
我连怎么开口都不会
I don't even know how I would go about it.
我最擅长的一手就是  上下打量一位女士
What I do is, I look a woman up and down,
然后说  "嘿  你好吗"
and I say..."Hey. How you doing?"
拜托
Oh, please!
嘿  你好吗
Hey. How you doing?
好吧  我决定了
You know what? I'm gonna do that.
我这就给他打电话  约他出来
I'm gonna call him up and I'm gonna ask him out.
有什么难的  说约就约
I can do that, ask him out.
"你好吗"
"How you doing?"
你好  约书亚
Hi, Joshua.
我是布明岱尔百货的瑞秋·葛林
It's Rachel Greene from Bloomingdale's.
对  我想问你...
Yeah, I was just wondering if you...
问你...
if you...
是不是把钱包丢在商场了
left your wallet at the store today?
我们检到一个皮夹...
We found a wallet, and we...
看驾照  真是好主意
The license? That is a good idea.
我看看  驾照是...
Well, let's see. This license belongs to...
一位名叫菲比的先生的
belongs to a Mr. Pheebs.
很抱歉在休息时间打扰你
So sorry to bother you at home.
明天见  再见
I'll see you tomorrow. Bye.
你真的这样干过几千次吗
You've done that a thousand times?
我可没你这么拐弯抹角
I've never done that.
我好怕他会拒绝
I just got so nervous that he'd say no.
你得给他点无法拒绝的东西  比如说...
You gotta give him something he can't say no to, like...
像尼克队的球票  找他去看尼克队的比赛
Knicks tickets. Invite the guy to a Knicks game.
我保证  他一定会答应
You're guaranteed he'll say yes.
真的吗  你觉得会有用
Really? You think that'll work?
当然  如果没用  富余的票归我成吗
Absolutely. And if doesn't, can I get the extra ticket?
什么声音
What the heck is that?
她给我打过电话吗
Did she call?
没有  抱歉
No. Sorry.
也许我应该打给她
Maybe I should call her.
别  忘了她吧  你不需要她
No. Forget her, man. You don't need her.
别再让自己窝火了
You don't need that.
没错  她的行为很不可原谅
He's right. What she did was unforgivable.
话虽没错  但要是我弄错了呢
Well, yeah, but, you know, what if I was wrong?
你怎么会弄错
How might you be wrong?
要是她没有真的跟那个人上床呢
What if she didn't actually sleep with the guy?
老兄  她亲口证实这一点了吗
Dude, tell me she actually told you this.
她不必亲口说出来
She didn't have to tell me.
我看了戏  他们在台上毫无激情
I saw the play. And there was no heat.
罗斯  帮我说句话
Back me up.
你的证据就是这个吗
That's all you're basing this on?
你这不是帮我说话
That's not backing me up!
你说过  "私下有激情  台上就没有...
Look, you said, "With the offstage and the heat..."
那只是个理论
That was just a theory.
很多理论都无法在现实中践行
There's a lot of theories that didn't pan out:
比如孤枪侠  共产主义  几何学
Lone gunman, communism, geometry.
天呐
Oh, my God!
你想不想去看篮球赛
Would you like to go to a basketball game with...
篮球  真巧  我正好有票...
It's funny, basketball, because I happen to have tickets...
谁喜欢尼克队
Who likes the Knick...
你觉得如何
What do you think?
就一个没对象的单身女郎而言...
Well, as a single woman, who is available...
我觉得你很帅
I think you look great.
没错  帅呆了
Oh, yeah. You look great.
看起来真配
This looks great.
你喜欢吗
So you like it?
很喜欢  我决定直接穿回家
I do. I love it. In fact, I think I'll wear it home.
太好了
Great.
谢谢你这几天的帮忙
Thank you so much for all your help.
那就这样喽
Well, I guess this is it.
多谢了
Thanks.
也许等开春我还会再来
Maybe I'll see you in the spring,
找你买泳衣
you know, for the bathing suits.
你不现在买吗
You don't want to do that now?
不用了
That's okay.
无论怎样  希望我们有缘相见吧
Anyway, hopefully, I'll see you around sometime.
篮球
Basketball!
什么
Sorry?
我有两张今晚尼克队的球票
I have two tickets to the Knicks game if you're interested...
想谢谢你这星期的惠顾
just as a thank-you for this week.
太好了
That would be great!
真的吗
Really?
对啊  简直太棒了
That would be fantastic!
我外甥最迷尼克队了
My nephew is crazy about the Knicks!
太棒了  太感谢你了  瑞秋
This is fantastic. Thank you so much, Rachel.
早安
Good morning.
我只是想来对你说声对不起
I just wanted to come over to say that I'm sorry.
我那天的做法真是太混蛋了
I acted like the biggest idiot in the world.
你完全理解你为何那样难过
And I can completely understand why you were so upset.
你真希望你能给我打电话
I really wish you'd called me.
我知道  我也很后梅没给你打
Yeah, I know. I wish I had too.
不过我觉得这是好事
I think this is a good thing, you know?
我们第一次吵了架
Cause we've had our first fight,
现在我们可以迈步向前了
and now we can move on.
至少我确定...
You know, I mean, I know for me, but...
-尼克的裤子  -对
- Nick's pants? - Yeah.
看来这第二次架  我们有得可吵了
I think our second fight is going to be a big one!
下次要怎么说
For next time, what do you say?
"我这儿有张多余的票"
"I have an extra ticket."
是多一张票  不是两张票
An extra ticket. Not two tickets.
我有一张多余的票
I have an extra ticket.
你第一次向男人提出约会
So, the first time you asked a guy out
却被拒绝了
he turned you down?
他没有拒绝  他去看球了  不是吗
He didn't turn me down. He's at the game, isn't he?
我约到他了  是我放了他的鸽子
I got the date. I'm just not on it.
都弄好了  来吧
Okay, it's ready.
-来吧  -什么弄好了
- Come on. - What's ready?
来就对了
Just come.
天哪
Oh, my God!
好漂亮啊
This is beautiful!
你不眠不休地整整忙了2天吗
Did you work for two days straight?
差不多
Pretty much.
觉得地板怎么样
What do you think of the floor?
没啥区别  看起来一样
I don't know. Looks the same.
以前你们铺的是地毯
You used to have carpet.
对啊
Oh, yeah.
我做了点心
I made snacks.
你们随便坐
Please, just hang out.
我要稍微眯一下
I'm just gonna rest my eyes for just a little bit.
莫妮卡  要不我们待会再来吧
Mon, do you want us to come back later?
不  留下来  继续聊天
No, no, no. Stay. Just keep talking.
我永远都是女主人
I'm always the hostess.
怎么样
How'd it go?
-她之前没跟他上过床  -太好了
- She wasn't sleeping with him. - Good!
可是现在跟他上过了
She is now.
这是什么意思
What are you saying?
意思是她很邪恶
I'm saying that she is a devil woman.
明白我的意思吧  你自以为很了解她
You know what I mean, you think you know a person,
可她一下就变了  跑去跟尼克滚床单
then they turn around and sleep with Nick.
尼克和他的胸肌  硕大的咪咪
Nick and his rock-hard pecs and his giant man-nipples.
我恨他  我也恨她
I hate him. And I hate her.
我不恨她  我爱她  都是我的错
I don't hate her. I love her. This is all my fault, really.
怎么会是你的错
How? How is it your fault?
因为我应该给她打个电话的
Because, I should have called.
要是那次大吵大闹之后我给她打过电话
If I had called her after our big, stupid fight,
她就不会跟尼克约会
she never would have gone out with Nick.
他们俩也就不会上床了
And they wouldn't have ended up in bed together.
是我自己亲手把她送到了他的怀里
I threw her at his man-nipples!
亲爱的  错不在你
Honey. This is not your fault.
就算你们俩大吵了一架
Just because you guys had a fight
她也不该跟别人上床
does not justify her sleeping with someone.
除非她以为他们分手了
Well, if she thought they were on a break...
瑞秋  你的某位客人
Rachel, one of your customers
好像把钱包落下了  名叫约书亚·柏根
seems to have left his billfold, a Joshua Burgen.
真的
Really?
麻烦你通知他
Will you call him?
好  没问题
Yes, I will. Absolutely.
瑞秋  你好
Hello, Rachel.
约书亚  你好
Hi, Joshua.
-我是故意把皮夹落下的  -真的吗
- I left my wallet here on purpose. - Really?
是的  因为我想再见到你
Yes. I just wanted to see you again.
我很荣幸
I'm glad.
瑞秋  我有话要对你说
Rachel, I'd like to say something to you.
什么话
Yes?
"你好吗"
"How you doing?"